The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Li Yuanfeng !
Ceng Niu...
How did his cultivation recover entirely in just a few years !?
You’ve got guts
to invade Xue Yue’s Ice and Snow Palace !
You're courting death !
Scram !
The power of this single word
was no weaker than Soul Transformation !
My two bodies merged together
are mutually enhancing each other.
This mutation didn't happen before.
In just a few years,
you’ve actually reached Late stage Soul Formation...
Today...
I will refine your soul !
Ceng Niu,
don't drag others
into our fight.
Fine.
Then the both of us
will settle
what happened that day.
Everyone, retreat 10 000 li !
Yes !
Soul Extracting Drum
I’ll make sure you don't make it out alive today !
This drum can disturb the Origin Soul.
Ceng Niu,
do you enjoy the taste of my Soul Extracting Drum ?
How can the drum fail ?!
Slash !
Is this the power of Soul Transformation ?
How could you have humiliated me like this
if not for my unhealed injuries !?
Even if my cultivation plummets today,
I will still kill you !
Tea Domain !
Soul Formation brat,
I will let you taste the strength of celestial spiritual energy !
Die !
The physical form of a Soul Transformation cultivator’s domain
is really strong !
Fall !
Ceng Niu,
I'll make sure
Xue Yue becomes your grave !
Soul Transformation spells are profound
but your celestial spiritual energy
is far too sparse.
I hoped this fight would help me grasp what Soul Transformation is
and you’ve indeed given me new insights.
Die !
If celestial spiritual energy can infuse a domain...
can Ancient God power do the same ?
What...
What domain is this ?!
Life and Death
Reincarnation !
His domain...
has already reached Soul Transformation ?!
So you are the one who sent that man back then...
Unseal !
You're unworthy
of these artifacts !
Go !
Seal !
Ceng Niu,
even if I die today,
I will drag you down with me !
Suzerain !
Exploding your Origin Soul ?
Try it.
I can tear open a spatial rift and leave anytime.
So the only ones who will die
are the people of Xue Yue...
Alright,
this old man has lost.
But Xue Yue is innocent,
don’t slaughter them all.
If you agree,
this old man will be at your mercy !
I want your Soul Transformation soul.
Suzerain...
My cultivation
has fallen to Nascent Soul !
I won’t kill you.
But from now on,
no Soul Formation cultivators are allowed to exist in Xue Yue
and cultivation sects are forbidden.
If you disobey...
I will come back.
Seal !
Back then, Xue Yue climbed over the Four Sects Alliance’s corpses
to become a rank 5 country.
But now...
the tide has turned...
As expected, this old man has a keen eye for talent !
This kid actually killed a Soul Transformation cultivator
with a Late stage Soul Formation cultivation !
Zhou Wutai\NMiddle stage Soul Formation
It's not an easy feat.
Brother Wang is truly extraordinary.
He turned Xue Yue to a rank 3 country
so you should help him too.
In that case,
you will go fight Liu Mei.
See how far her Thousand Illusions Ruthless Domain
has progressed.
Understood.
Zhuque Zi’s disciples can’t be underestimated.
Especially Qian Feng,
he's the most gifted cultivator I’ve ever seen.
Zi Xin
was once his cauldron,
she may become a crack in his Dao Heart someday.
As for Liu Mei’s domain,
Zhou Wutai’s Emotion Severing Domain
might stand a chance against it !
Liu Mei seems drawn to Wang Lin’s domain...
This kid
might be the key to breaking Zhuque Zi’s game !
Senior Brother,
our wager back then
stipulated 1 000 years of seclusion.
In 12 years,
this old man will be free.
Then we’ll see who will inherit the title of Suzaku.
Who knows what will happen...
Ceng Niu’s attack on Xue Yue
ended with him singlehandedly
slaying its Suzerain,
sealing all the cultivators
and demoting the country to rank 3 !
The mighty Li Yuanfeng
has been
defeated !
Li Yuanfeng was just a trash forcibly raised to Soul Transformation.
Ceng Niu,
if you can kill the Giant Demon Clan's Ancestor
then you’ll barely qualify
as my opponent.
Senior,
I used Soul Search on Li Yuanfeng
but found no clues about you.
You said that
I'll be able to wake you at Soul Transformation.
That must be because I need celestial spiritual energy.
Li Yuanfeng's cultivation was forcibly raised
and he lacked celestial spiritual energy.
But the Giant Demon Clan's Ancestor
has a genuine cultivation.
With his teleportation spell,
even Sun Tai feared him.
I'm not sure
if I can fight him.
That day, the Giant Demon Clan's Ancestor insisted on taking my body...
I have my own reasons.
He must have learned
about the Heaven Defying Bead from his clansmen.
Once he recovers from his injuries,
he’ll surely come back for me.
Do I fight
or do I flee ?
If I fight,
the outcome is uncertain.
But if I flee,
I will miss my best chance to kill him !
Who is it ?
I am Ouyang Tian,
I was sent by Ancestor Du Tian
to deliver something to you.
Ancestor Du Tian knows your plans
so he instructed me
to give you this.
Little friend Ceng Niu,
I cannot leave seclusion
but I can offer you this instead.
This jade slip
details how to counter the Giant Demon Clan's teleportation spell.
So that's how...
And this other item
is something you’ve seen before.
The Billion-Soul Flag ?!
This is just an illusory sub flag
that can only be used twice.
This sub flag has a third of the true flag's power.
The 12 golden soul fragments
are past Sect Leaders who reached Soul Transformation.
With them,
this flag’s power
is no joke.
To control this Soul Flag
you must cast
the Soul Sealing spell.
What a powerful pressure !
Seal !
Alright,
I’ve given you everything.
Little friend,
I will wait for you at the Soul Refining Sect.
I will never forget your kindness.
Giant Demon Clan Ancestor,
you won't escape this !
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.